healthcarejobsite.com 2014-09-25

# Privacy Policy | Beyond.com

## Collection and Use of Information

When you register with this site or one of the web sites in our network (collectively, the "Beyond Network" or the "Site"), we ask you for personal information, such as your name, phone number, and email address. We use this information to process your requests, to communicate with you about the status of your requests, and to review and improve the service we provide to you. We may also use your email address to send you information about your account, such as newsletters to which you are subscribed during registration, as well as messages about any special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys, Beyond services, account updates, services that may be of interest to you, or administrative messages regarding your account. You can manage your email list options under your account user settings.

In addition, we may send job alert and other relevant text messages to your mobile phone number if you provide your mobile phone number and request these text alerts when you register with our Site. Shortly after opting-in to this alert feature, you will receive a text welcome message. You can opt-out of receiving these alerts by texting "STOP" to 97900. You will receive a confirmation text that you have opted-out.

By registering on or using our Site, you consent to the disclosure of your personal information to our partners and affiliates. Beyond does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with third parties or non-affiliated companies, except as otherwise disclosed in this policy, or under the following circumstances:

We disclose information:

  * to companies and individuals we employ to perform services on our behalf,
  * if legally required to do so,
  * to protect the rights or property of the Beyond Network or our affiliated companies, or
  * to protect the personal safety of users or the general public.

Additionally, information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership of our company.

In order to serve you better and more efficiently, we may also share anonymous aggregated information about users with our partners and other third parties.

We collect information from our users at several different points on the Site. When you first register with us, we ask for your email address. At this time, we may subscribe you to various email publications. You can unsubscribe from any or all publications at any time. If you are a registered member, click here to access your account and manage your email options. We will delete data on our Site that you have provided to us, upon request, through our Contact Us form.

We also offer an affiliate program, where affiliate members direct customers to the Beyond Network through links on their Web sites. We ask affiliates for information, including their site name (URL), mailing address, primary contact, pay-to address, technical contact, and other site-related information, to determine whether a site will be included in our network. The information collected from our affiliates is used strictly for our affiliate program; none of this information is used for general marketing purposes.

In some cases our software and Site are utilized by our partners in a business alliance via their web community. In these cases, the information collected on our Site is available to both companies.

You should be aware that any personal information (such as email address or resumes), which you voluntarily display or distribute on the Beyond Network and on the Internet can be collected and used by others, no different than posting this information in a newspaper. This may result in your receiving unsolicited messages from third parties for which Beyond.com is not responsible and has no ability to affect. If you click on a third party job posting and provide that party with your personal information, we have no responsibility or control over that information.

The Site uses the ClickTale web analytics service, which is not owned, operated or controlled by Beyond.com. We use the information collected by ClickTale service to improve your user experience. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity, as well as any text you type in this Site. ClickTale does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter into this Site. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information, see [Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx). You may disable this Service at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>.

Back to top

* * *

## Viewing and Updating Your Information on the Network

You always have complete access to the information you have provided to the Beyond Network. You can make changes to this information to update your account anytime. If you are a registered member, you may click here to manage your information.

Back to top

* * *

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive and/or your mobile device. In general, we use cookies and similar technologies to help us better serve you and improve your experience on our Site. As you browse areas of the Beyond Network, cookies may be placed on your computer's hard drive and/or your mobile device which may allow us to collect information, such as your internet protocol address and mobile device identifier. Cookies allow us to track your account so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our Site. Cookies also allow us to provide certain services and features to you. You may refuse cookies in your browser, but doing so may result in certain services and features not functioning properly.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our Site. These advertisers may also serve cookies when you click on advertisements on the Site, or use pixel tags, web beacons, or similar technologies to collect non-personally identifiable aggregated information when users visit the Site in order to provide advertisements on our Site, other sites, and other forms of media about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This common practice is known as "online behavioral advertising" or "interest based advertising". To learn more about this practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, please visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. In addition, if you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, you may visit each ad network's web site individually and opt-out. We do not have access to personal information, if any, gathered by advertisers.

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including on your mobile device) to enable you to receive customized ads or content, including through online behavioral advertising. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.beyond.com/content/cookies.asp.

Back to top

* * *

## Cached Information

There may be instances where information you have submitted to Beyond.com is temporarily cached or stored by another site, such as Google.com, even after such information has been removed from the Beyond Network. These sites are maintained by third parties not controlled by Beyond.com. Accordingly, Beyond.com expressly disclaims any responsibility for the cached information displayed by these third party web sites.

Back to top

* * *

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Back to top

* * *

## Links

The Beyond Network contains links to other sites. You may have arrived at this website by clicking on a link from a Beyond.com affiliate or other affiliate. If so, you should be aware that Beyond.com may share your information with that affiliate and the affiliate may use the information in accordance with its privacy policy instead of ours.

Back to top

* * *

## Recommend a Friend or Colleague

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend or colleague about our Site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to visit the Site or review the content selected by a user. We then store this information in our databases. The friend may contact us to request that we remove this information at any time.

Back to top

* * *

## Security and Access

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

When you place an order online at the Beyond Network, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. This Site uses a service company to process its credit card transactions.

Users should not post personal information to any site if they are uncomfortable with the security of the site. If you have any questions, please contact us.

Back to top

* * *

## Children

This site is not intended for children under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly or specifically collect information about children. This Site does not and will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of this Site, we encourage you to use web-filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the Site. For children 14 and up (high-school age), we also encourage you to participate in your child's experience with our Site. With a little guidance, this Site can prove very useful in finding a part-time or summer job for your child, as well as providing them with excellent career counseling information.

Back to top

* * *

## California Residents

California law permits California residents to request and receive certain information about disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and a user of the Site and wish to request this information, please contact us or write to us at Beyond.com, 1060 First Avenue, Suite 100, King of Prussia, PA 19406, Attention: Customer Service. You may request this information once a year, and there is no charge for the request.

Back to top

* * *

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If at any point you have questions or concerns about Beyond.com's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

Back to top

* * *
